#### Cookie Settings

**Accept Optional Cookies:**

Tellwut uses advertising to support the platform and to provide you with access to our services. We use advertising technologies from third-party vendors, including Publisher First, Inc. dba Freestar and Google AdSense, to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. This may include the use of cookies, web beacons, or other similar technologies to help them better understand your preferences based on your online activity. For details on how these work please visit our [Privacy Policy](https://www.tellwut.com/privacy_policy) under “Advertising” section.

Please note that if you choose to disable cookies, you may still see advertisements on our website, but they may not be tailored to your interests.

We take your privacy very seriously and strive to be transparent about our advertising practices. If you have any questions or concerns about our use of advertising technologies, please contact us at [support@tellwut.com](mailto:support@tellwut.com)

**Strictly Necessary Cookies** → **Always Active**

These cookies are necessary for the website to function and cannot be switched off in our systems. They are usually only set in response to actions made by you which amount to a request for services, such as setting your privacy preferences, logging in or filling in forms. You can set your browser to block or alert you about these cookies, but some parts of the site will not then work. These cookies do not store any personally identifiable information.

* **Targeting Cookies**
    
    These cookies may be set through our site by our advertising partners. They may be used by those companies to build a profile of your interests and show you relevant adverts on other sites. They do not store directly personal information but are based on uniquely identifying your browser and internet device. If you do not allow these cookies, you will experience less targeted advertising.

* * *

**Sale of Personal Data**

Under the California Consumer Privacy Act, you have the right to opt-out of the sale of your personal information to third parties. These cookies collect information for analytics and to personalize your experience with targeted ads. You may exercise your right to opt out of the sale of personal information by using this toggle switch. If you opt out we will not be able to offer you personalized ads and will not hand over your personal information to any third parties. Additionally, you may contact our legal department for further clarification about your rights as a California consumer by using this Exercise My Rights link.

If you have enabled privacy controls on your browser (such as a plugin), we have to take that as a valid request to opt-out. Therefore we would not be able to track your activity through the web. This may affect our ability to personalize ads according to your preferences.

* **Performance Cookies**
    
    These cookies allow us to count visits and traffic sources so we can measure and improve the performance of our site. They help us to know which pages are the most and least popular and see how visitors move around the site.    All information these cookies collect is aggregated and therefore anonymous. If you do not allow these cookies we will not know when you have visited our site, and will not be able to monitor its performance.

Accept Selected

This website uses cookies to enhance user experience and to analyze performance and traffic on our website. We also share information about your use of our site with our social media, advertising, and analytics partners.

Cookie settings

Sign Up Login

EARN

REWARDS LIVE

Member polls

* More Categories

Rewards

Amazon gift card

Take surveys and collect rewards from the industry-leading e-commerce website, Amazon.com, Via "amazon gift cards". The more you take or create survey, larger the amazon gift card you earn.

Privacy Policy
==============

Paradigm Sample, LLC. ("PS") is a US market research company that oversees operation  of [www.tellwut.com](http://www.tellwut.com/), a social networking site (the "Site") together with its Canadian affiliate, who owns the Site (individually and collectively referred to in this policy as  “We” ).  The Site which allows users to post online surveys, answer surveys, either Internal  surveys or third party surveys ( "External Surveys") from other companies ( "External Survey Company" or External Survey Companies") engaged by PS.  The Site also allows participants to  refer friends to the Site to similarly post and answer internal surveys and External Surveys, and provide certain personal information about themselves all while earning rewards that can be redeemed for merchandise under the TW Rewards Program. The Site also allows businesses and other organizations or individuals to participate in a variety of fee-based programs regarding the posting of surveys and the collection of survey data.

This **Privacy Policy** ("Policy") and the **Terms and Conditions** contain important details about registration and participation in the Site and the TW Rewards Program. Please read them carefully. This Policy was last modified on: Novemer 22, 2023.

Any modifications to this policy will be posted on the Site, so you should check the "last modified" date of the Policy periodically. The latest online version of the Policy is the governing version.

**Copyright**

Please reference the bottom of this page for links to any copyright related matters and policies.

**Our Commitment to Privacy**

This Policy and the Privacy Notice in the Terms and Conditions describe how We collect, use and disclose your personal information and the choices available to you about what information you disclose and how We use it. Visitors to the Site are free to browse without providing any personal information. However, choosing not to provide us  with certain personal information may result in you being unable to use functions of the Site such as posting surveys, enrolling in the Program, and earning rewards and points in the TW Rewards Program. Visitors to the Site who register to become members (“Members”) are automatically enrolled in the TW Rewards Program; instructions on becoming a member can be found on the home page of the Site.

**Do Not Sell My Personal Information**

We will not sell Personal Information without explicit consent from Members. The section below entitled “**_Do We disclose personal information to third parties?_**” describes who has access to your information and to what end. Members have full control in updating their personal information and to opt out of the Program entirely. More details about opt-out process can be found on “**_How do I opt-out of information I have provided to US through the Site?_**” section.   

**Who can use the Site?**

You must be at least eighteen (18) years old. Only residents of Canada or the United States can participate in the TW Rewards Program.

**What kind of personal information is collected on the Site****?**

We collect personal information when and if you register for the Site. Upon registering as a Member, We collect- your first and last name, unique email address, gender, and date of birth ("Account Information"). After registering, a Member has the option to provide more personal information, namely "Additional Personal Information" (e.g. your education level, yearly income, type of residence, (rent or own), marital status, ethnicity, occupation, and whether or not you have children, ages of children) all of which may be added to from time to time and "Contact and Shipping Information" (e.g. your address and phone number). We do not collect personal information from visitors to the Site who do not elect to register as Members.

We may also collect  background information about your computer hardware and software (if applicable) (“Background Information”). This information may include (among other things) your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times, and referring website addresses. We use this information to operate our  Site and its interface and connection to the Web  mobile sites, to maintain quality of our services, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Site and services

For the purposes of this Policy, a reference to "Personal Information" hereafter includes Account Information, Additional Personal Information, Background Information and Contact and Shipping Information as well as Billing Address as provided to us in registering for the TW Reward Program.

**How can I review, edit and/or request access to my personal information?**

After registration, Members can choose a profile picture to associate with their account. Your profile picture can be edited once you have logged in by clicking on the "Profile" in the top right hand corner of the screen.

You can also contact our Privacy Office by emailing [support@tellwut.com](mailto:support@tellwut.com) to access, change or update your Personal Information or for more information about our use of your Personal Information. We will do its best to respond to your request within thirty (30) days of its receipt. However, We reserve the right to take an additional thirty (30) days if:

* Responding to you in the original 30 days would unreasonably interfere with TW's activities, or
* Additional time is required to conduct consultations or to convert Personal Information to an alternate format to accommodate your request.

Please note there are certain situations, where permitted by law, when we cannot disclose Personal Information to you. This includes situations where the P-personal Information contains references to other individuals, the Personal Iinformation is subject to attorney-client or litigation privilege, or there are legal, security or proprietary reasons for not disclosing the information.

How is my Personal Information used?

We may use your Personal Information in the following ways:

* To process and send Members merchandise redeemed with their TW Points,
* To analyze demographic information with respect to survey responses. 
* For our internal purposes, such as to identify website usage trends, for audits, to enhance our website and address problems, to track compliance with the Site's Terms and Conditions, and to protect the security and integrity of the Site.
* To contact you regarding your transactions with us, such as survey approval or disapproval or shipping problems associated with rewards for Members.
* To send you emails related to the any program on the Site that are administrative, for example, emails about your account ("Program Emails").
* To send you promotional emails about the products and services available as part of the TW Reward Program or surveys.
* Members may also send surveys from the Site to email addresses in their possession. On sending these surveys, the recipient of the survey will see the Member's name and email address.
* We has various checks and balances to determine if a Member is random clicking and or using computerized techniques to perform automated voting on online surveys. These techniques will raise a flag in the Member Site profile, only accessible by the Site administrators. Members are subject to  reward forfeiture and account closure as per the Terms and Conditions.
* We  may also share your Personal Information (but non-identifiable data) with our clients who request this information for use in aggregate analysis. For example, We may provide a client with data collected from a recent survey, with variables such as age, household income, or gender from the registration survey appended to the file. This is primarily designed to save our panelists time and effort, so they do not need to re-answer these questions on each and every survey. This appended data, however, will never include personally identifiable information such as your full name, mailing address, or email address.

**Do We disclose your Personal Information to third parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer Personal Information outside the Site Personal Information on the Site would be transferred to  any person or entity which obtains the business, franchise, or assets constituting the Site.

We may allow authorized third party service providers access to Personal Information collected though the Site to perform services on their behalf, including access to Personal Information required for reward redemption. Our service providers are required to provide appropriate protection for all Personal Information and to limit their use of such information to providing services on our behalf. These service providers may be in another country, and the Personal Information may be subject to disclosure in accordance with the applicable laws of that jurisdiction, which may create a different privacy regime from your country of residence.

We may provide Personal Information of Members who take External Surveys to the External Survey Company when this information is required for matching to a third party database for member authentication or data matching. In all cases we require that the External Survey Company  not use or disclose the Member’s identifiable information for any other purpose, including, without limitation, marketing third-party services, selling to or influencing the opinions or decisions of any Members or contacting the Member in any manner under any circumstances for any purpose without the Member's approval.

We may also share your Personal Information including  social-demographic information, with a unique identification number ("UID"), postal code, gender, marital status, education, ethnicity/race (where permitted by applicable law), employment related information, and non-personally identifiable information on household members, with External Survey Companies for the purpose of identifying survey opportunities that you may be eligible for through the External Survey Companies. If you are eligible for a survey opportunity, the External Survey Company will provide your unique identification number and a survey link to us and we will invite you to participate in the survey. We will not share your name, email address, or phone number with these External Survey Companies. In connection with the sharing of your information with an External Survey Company, your information may be transferred and stored outside of your country of residence. If you have any questions about this data sharing please contact [support@tellwut.com](mailto:support@tellwut.com) or alternatively you can opt-out of the by unsubscribing here: [https://www.tellwut.com/account/unsubscribe](https://www.tellwut.com/account/unsubscribe). Your participation in such survey opportunities does not entitle you to any benefits offered by, or membership with, the External Survey Companies.

In addition, We may be required to disclose Personal Iinformation collected through the Site to: (1) satisfy or comply with any law, regulation or other governmental or law enforcement request; (2) protect our or any other person's rights, privacy or safety; (3) protect against fraud or other illegal activity; (4) allow us to pursue remedies or limit damages that we may sustain in a legal action; or (5) enforce the Terms.

**What information will other visitors to the Site be able to see?**

Remember, your responses to a survey will not be personally identifiable or publicly disclosed. However, any Member's User Names are associated with any surveys or comments that they post on the Site and can be seen by visitors to the site.

Members within the Site will be able to see another Member's country along with state/province and name if the Member has agreed to allow this information to be visible to their friends. These privacy settings are adjustable under the "Settings" tab accessible on the "Account" page. Members and Guest members will also be able to see another Member's User Name associated with any surveys or comments, as well as their profile pictures.

Because Members' User Names will be publicly displayed, it is strongly recommended that it not contain any information that could identify you, such as your last name.

Members may email each other through the Site's internal email system and send friend requests to other Tellwut members through the internal system.

**How do I opt-out?**

Any Member who does not wish to receive further Program Emails or Online Surveys or Promotional Emails from us can opt-out of receiving such emails or mail by:

* Following the instructions in each such email where applicable, or
* By emailing us at [support@tellwut.com](mailto:support@tellwut.com).
* By adjusting your settings at [https://www.tellwut.com/account/settings](https://www.tellwut.com/account/settings).

Please be sure to include your full name and email address when you subscribed to the Site. It may take up to ten (10) days to process a request received by email.

If you change your mind and would like to start receiving Program Emails or Surveys or Promotional Emails from us again, you can do so by emailing us at [support@tellwut.com](mailto:support@tellwut.com) or adjusting your settings at [https://www.tellwut.com/account/settings](https://www.tellwut.com/account/settings).

If you want to delete your account or permanently opt out from the Site, please email us at [support@tellwut.com](mailto:support@tellwut.com). Your account cannot be reinstated once it has been deleted and you will lose any unredeemed points. All the Personal information (such as email, first and last name, address, phone number, etc.,) you shared previously will be deleted from our systems and we are not able to retrieve it. Comments on member surveys will be anonymized. If your membership has been permanently deleted, but you wish to become a Member again, you will need to sign up as a new Member. It may take up to ten (10) days to process a request received by email.

**Does the Site use cookies?**

Yes, the Site uses cookies. A "cookie" is a small data file that is stored on your computer when you visit a website, such as the Site. We uses cookies to optimize a user's experience on the Site. The cookie information is an anonymous profile that helps us to determine the user's origin. We also use cookies as session ID markers to recognize a visitor when they return to the Site and confirm that Members are logged in.

We do not track a visitor's behavior on the Site through use of cookies and no Personal Information is stored regarding the visitor. We do not look at any other cookies nor do we store information for other sites to use. You can configure your browser not to accept cookies. However, you will not be able to access certain features of the Site, such as logging in, answering survey questions, or posting surveys.

Some of the External Surveys We offer are related to online or mobile ad exposure programs. To facilitate participation in these programs through  We or the External Survey Company or their client may write, set or read first and third party cookies, locally shared/stored objects, flash cookies, and/or any other related technology (herein referred to as "Digital Cookies"). A unique identification number and a source identification number may be stored in the Digital Cookie. If you have viewed or interacted with the online ad or promotion, the External Survey Company will send us your unique identification number and a link to the specific survey offer which you may access through an email from us or via the  Site. Survey participation is completely voluntary and you can opt-out at any time.

**Advertising**

Tellwut uses advertising to support the platform and to provide you with access to our services. We use advertising technologies from third-party vendors, including Publisher First, Inc. dba Freestar ("Freestar") and Google AdSense, to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. This may include the use of cookies, web beacons, or other similar technologies to help them better understand your preferences based on your online activity.

Publisher First, Inc. dba Freestar ("Freestar") is a technology company that specializes in providing ad monetization solutions and services for online publishers, including Tellwut. Freestar will collect and use certain data for advertising purposes. To learn more about Freestar’s data usage, click [here](https://freestar.com/privacy-policy/).

Google AdSense is a program run by Google that allows website publishers in the Google Network of content sites to serve automatic text, image, video, or interactive media advertisements, that are targeted to site content and audience. Google AdSense uses cookies to serve ads based on your visits to this and other websites. You can read Google's privacy policy here: [Privacy Policy – Privacy & Terms – Google](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en).

Please note that if you choose to disable cookies, you may still see advertisements on our website, but they may not be tailored to your interests.

We take your privacy very seriously and strive to be transparent about our advertising practices. If you have any questions or concerns about our use of advertising technologies, please contact us at [support@tellwut.com](mailto:support@tellwut.com).

**Does the Site use Google Analytics?**

Yes, the Site uses Google Analytics, a web analytics tool provided by Google, Inc. ("Google") that helps us understand how visitors engage with our website. Google Analytics uses cookies and IP addresses. The information generated by cookies about the use of our website and your IP address will be transmitted and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information to evaluate how visitors use our website, compile reports on website activity for us and provide other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Google Analytics collects information anonymously, and will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. To opt-out of Google Analytics, you can install Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-On. For information about and to install Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on, click here: [http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en) For more information related to Google Analytics, click here: [http://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html](http://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html)

**How do We use IP addresses or website log files?**

An IP address is a number automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet Service Provider (ISP). It is logged automatically in our server log files whenever you visit the Site, along with the time of your visit and the pages you visited on the Site. It is standard practice on the Internet to collect IP addresses.

We use IP addresses to ensure a survey is only answered once, as well as to analyze trends such as website usage levels, administer the Site, track users' movements, and gather broad demographic information for our internal use. IP addresses are associated to a Member's Account for ensuring compliance with Terms and Conditions relating to one account per household and non acceptance of Members using Proxy IP's.

**What about third party links on the Site?**

This Site may contain links to other websites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you will be entering another website. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policy may differ from ours. Including a link to a third party website on the Site does not mean or imply that We endorse the third party website.

**How do We protect personal information collected on the Site?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of all Personal Information provided on the Site. We use physical (e.g. locked filing cabinets, restrict building access, alarm systems), organizational (e.g. security clearances, access to personal information on a "need to know" basis only, employee training), and technological (e.g. encryption and password protection) safeguards to help prevent unauthorized access to personal information.

All Personal Information collected is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of employees with special access rights to such systems as well as by authorized service providers. Our employees are required to sign confidentiality agreements on employment with the company. Authorized service providers performing services on our behalf  are required to provide similarly appropriate protection for all personal information and to limit their use of such information to providing services on our behalf (see "Do We disclose Personal Information to third parties?").

Members also have a significant role in protecting their Personal Iinformation. No one can access your account without knowing your password. So, we suggest selecting a password that is hard to "crack" (e.g., use numbers with upper and lower case letters) and not sharing your User Name and password with anyone. Your password can be changed at any time by logging in to your account, clicking on "Account" in the top right corner, and selecting the "Settings" tab.

**How long do We retain Personal Information?**

Any Personal Information you provide to us and any content posted on the Site is kept as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Policy, unless a longer retention period is required by law. When we no longer needs to retain your Personal Information, it will be destroyed in a manner that ensures its private and confidential nature is preserved.

**How is my consent obtained by Us?**

For all users (Unregistered Users & Members), your use of the Site constitutes your consent to the collection and use of non-personal information such as cookie information, website logs and IP addresses by us as described in this Policy. By providing your Account Information on registering as Members, you consent to the collection and use of any Personal Information by us as described in this Policy and agree to receive email survey invitations to participate in surveys.

We will post changes to this Policy at [www.tellwut.com](http://www.tellwut.com/), as described above. Your continued use of the Site will constitute your consent to the changes to the Policy. It is your responsibility to check the "last modified" date of the Policy periodically.

**How do I contact Us?**

You have a right to receive access to Personal Information we have on file and the right to challenge the accuracy and completeness of your information and have it amended as appropriate.

In some circumstances permitted by law, We  may not be able to provide access to your information or to all of it. For example, We will not provide access to information if doing so would reveal personal information about a third party, would reveal confidential commercial information, or if it is protected by solicitor-client privilege or was generated in the course of a formal dispute resolution process.

We welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy. For anything to do with this Policy or to challenge our compliance with this Policy, please contact us at:

Email: [support@tellwut.com](mailto:support@tellwut.com)

We will inform individuals making inquiries or lodging privacy complaints about its inquiry or complaint procedures, as applicable. Where a complaint is justified, We will implement measures, including amending the Policy and its practices, if required.

**Legal Disclaimer**

This Policy is subject to applicable national privacy laws such as the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA), Canada's Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act (PIPEDA). We reserve the right to change the Policy at any time and at its sole discretion. Please also read our Terms establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of the Site .

**Copyright Policy and Claims**

Please see our [Copyright Policy and Claims Page](https://www.tellwut.com/copyright_policy_and_claims) for information on DMCA registration and Take Down policy.

© 2023 Paradigm. All rights reserved.

Member polls

* More Categories

FOLLOW US ON

Tellwut

Member Polls

Survey for Voters

Surveys for Organizations

Once you have registered your account at Tellwut you can start earning rewards. You receive a fast 100 points to register and then another quick 100 points when you provide additional information about yourself. This information allows us to invite you to special higher point value surveys, but don't worry; your responses are anonymous and co-mingled with everyone else. Also, be sure to key in your correct address as this is where your reward will be mailed. Once you have joined Tellwut you are an official "Tellwutter" and can give your opinion and Tell Wut You Think! For each survey you answer you collect reward points. You are never disqualified from answering a survey! All you have to do is log into Tellwut and start answering surveys and earning rewards. New surveys are posted daily. Bigger valued surveys are emailed to you, so don't forget to check "send me promotions" when signing up and watch your email for special invitation.

Tellwut provides numerous ways to make money and get paid. Just by joining and answering surveys while you are logged in, you can rack up points quickly. You can earn more rewards by referring friends and creating your own online surveys. The first redemption level is 4,000 points and we have many exciting reward options available. You can cash in and redeem your Tellwut rewards for various prizes like Amazon Gift cards, Walmart Gift Cards, Gap Gift Cards, Future Shop Gift Cards (Canada only), Home Depot Gift Cards (US only), Best Buy Gift Cards (Canada only) or save your points up for a Motorola XOOM Android Tablet.

Tellwut offers a unique way for its Voter Panel to earn extra reward points for cash. Create your own online survey using Tellwut's proprietary software tool. All you have to do is click on "Create Survey" and choose your survey type. Choose "Single Question Survey" for only one question or if you would like to ask more than one question, choose "Multi-question Survey". Type in your questions and pick your answer type. You can choose from a wide variety of answer options like, Yes/No, Fill in the Blank, Multiple Choice – single answer or Multiple Choice – multiple answers. Don't forget to save your survey and when you are happy with it, just click publish. Once approved Tellwut reward points will automatically be deposited into your account. Send a private survey to your friends or that special someone, or ask the Tellwut Voter panel that question you have always wondered about.

Are you getting a group together and want to have your own "Survey Says" style party? Create a number of thought provoking questions a few weeks in advance and start posting them on Tellwut. Surprise your friends with the questions and see what their answers are versus the Tellwut panel. Your questions and answers are guaranteed to provide some stimulating discussion and make your party memorable. Alternatively, do you want to know what your friends want to eat, what activity they want to do, or what food they may be allergic too? Post a private survey to the group and make sure your event runs smoothly!

Tellwut provides an easy to use online survey software tool on its robust proprietary online survey platform. Design your survey in minutes! It's as easy as 1-2-3. We can also provide assistance and recommendations on your survey topics. Do you have paper survey results that you need to analyze? Key survey results as you canvass people over the phone. No messy tabulating later. View your results in an easy-to-read presentation.

Want to post your surveys to your website, on Facebook or on your other social media pages? No web server, no software coding, no programming maintenance needed! Secure instance, either for public or for private surveys. Just copy the private link provided and customize your hyperlink. Using our business software tools, you can direct your responders back to you.

If you are interested in market research on a specific service or topic, Tellwut's proprietary survey software tools allow you to direct your surveys to the demographic of your choice. Not sure what your demographic is? Post the survey on Tellwut's open forum and analyze the results on key demographics like gender, age, location, and more.

Tellwut has a very active voter panel which can provide you with an instantaneous online feedback loop. If you want to gain valuable insight into your product, service or idea, put your questions out to the Tellwut panel. If you want to target your research to a specific demographic, we'll email your survey for you to your target audience. Watch your responses come in online. Reporting tools available and results are private.

2024 Tellwut ® - [Online Surveys, Opinion Polls & Questions](https://www.tellwut.com/)

* Surveys: **89,393**

* Voters: **2,650,872**

* Cookie settings

* Light / Dark / Auto
